原创翻译  双语字幕
最新连载海外影视剧下载
请登陆 www.YYeTs.com
仅供交流学习  禁止商用盈利
翻译      Margaery  capitaljack  秋乙一
翻译      吃冰棒  半半子七  一点都不酷喵
校对      free维塔
时间轴      Avis
后期      你是不是饿得慌
总监      free维塔
公告     人人影视永久官方网站 www.YYeTs.com
傲骨之战
第一季 第八集
雷迪克&博斯曼&科斯达律所
当我环顾这个房间  我看到了
When I look around this room, I see the future,
用力量和韧性铸就的未来
defined by strength, resilience,
以及团结协作的决心
and the determination to work together.
当我们站在佩图斯桥的中央
So, now, when we stood in the center of the Pettus Bridge...
看着阿拉巴马州的塞尔玛
and that's Selma, Alabama...
1965年由马丁·路德·金带领的争取黑人投票权的游行
同时  我们又惊讶地看见了这些士兵
we looked and we saw these troopers at the other end,
他们的步枪交织在一起
and their rifles in tow, and we were surprised, you know.
但我们高贵的灵魂当中
But not one of our precious souls
谁都没有表现出任何一丝恐惧
expressed an ounce of fear.
如果你有值得为之反抗的事情
If you have anything worth fighting against,
无论是有失公正
whether it's injustice
还是失控的总统
or an out of control president...
你们都要大无畏地站在对立面上
you stand in the face of opposition fearlessly.
这就是这家律所要诠释的精神
Now, that's what this firm represents.
这就是你们要做的  你们都是战士
That's what you all are. You're all fighters.
人人皆是
Each and every one of you.
你们是战士
You're fighters.
我就说这些
I'm done for the day.
好的  好的
Okay, okay.
我们的律所还是要干活的
We still have a firm to operate.
而且我们不想把创办合伙人搞得精疲力尽
Besides, we don't want to exhaust - our founding partner.
没关系  芭芭拉  好了
That's all right, Barbara. All right, now.
大家都回去工作吧
Back to work, y'all.
你知道他要来吗
Did you know he was coming?
不知道
No.
你知道他想要什么吗
You know what he wants?
想看看我们在做什么吧
To see how we're doing.
我看更像是抱怨我们的所作所为
Complain about how we're doing, more like.
-阿德里安  -卡尔
- Adrian. - Carl.
-你怎么样  -挺好的  你呢
- How you doing? - All right. How you doing?
挺好挺好
Good, good.
你有空吗
Hey, uh, you got a minute?
有空  有空  进来吧
Yeah, yeah, go on in.
-这吗  好的  -对  继续
- In here? Okay. - Yeah, go on.
芭芭拉
Barbara.
黛安
Diane.
你确定吗
Are you sure?
我了解卡尔
I know Carl;
他很有可能只想谈谈警方暴力执法的案子
he probably just wants to talk about the police brutality cases.
来吧
Come on.
还是咱们冠名合伙人之间吧
Maybe just the name partners?
-也许...  -当然
- You know, maybe... - Oh, of course.
等等
Well, wait, wait.
黛安是执行委员会的  卡尔
Diane's on the executive committee, Carl.
让她留在这个应该是个好主意
Probably a good idea that she be here.
哥们  这边到底什么情况啊
Hey, man, what the hell is going on here?
我一转身
I turn my back,
咱们就被起诉了
and we're being indicted.
我们不是被起诉  卡尔
We were not indicted, Carl.
什么  大陪审团对你穷追不舍的
What, you got grand juries all over your butt, man.
那是因为我们尽了本分
That's because we're doing our jobs.
与此同时  我还是看「洛杉矶时报」才知道
In the meantime, I have to find out from the L.A. Times
你跟硅谷里
that you just signed with
最白的公司之一签了合同
one of the whitest companies in Silicon Valley.
你真的是在抱怨我们拿下了一家
You really complaining because we brought in a company
每年能带来8600万收入的公司吗
worth $86 million a year?
那公司只有百分之二的员工是黑人
Yeah, two percent black employment.
那跟我们一点关系都没有  卡尔
We don't have anything to do with that, Carl.
我们要生存  卡尔
We have to make a living, Carl.
还有  我最近总是接到客户的电话
Now, in the meantime, I've been receiving these calls
说感觉到自己
from these clients who are feeling
-被忽视了  -谁  告诉我是谁
- that they're being neglected. - Who? Tell me, who?
奈杰尔  他说他打电话都找不到你
Nigel. He says he can't get you on the phone.
-奈杰尔·罗杰斯  -是的
- Nigel Rogers? - Yeah.
奈杰尔·罗杰斯自从2009年开始
Nigel Rogers has not made money
就没给律所赚过一分钱  卡尔
for this firm since 2009, Carl!
没准就是因为你不给他回电话
Maybe because you have not returned his call.
你们没事吧  听着像吵架
You all right? Sounds like a fight.
没什么  友好协商纷争而已
Uh, no, just a friendly disagreement.
什么事
What's up?
我就是打电话确认一下咱俩今晚是不是照旧
I'm just checking to see if we're still on for tonight?
-是的  老地方吗  -不  计划有变
- Yeah. Same place, right? - No, change of plans.
-什么  -画廊
- What? - Art gallery.
不行  人太多了
No. Too many people.
得了  那也就能有八个人
Ah, come on. There'll be, like, eight people there.
没人会看到咱俩的  我到洗手间里给你口
No one will see us. I'll go down on you in the bathroom.
你上次就是这么说的
You promised that last time.
是的  这次  我发毒誓
Yeah, well, this time, I double-dog swear.
我把具具发给你
I'll text the deets.
不许说"具具"  我特别讨厌你说"具具"
Don't say "Deets." I hate it when you say "Deets."
具体情况的简称
具具  具具  具具  具具
Deet-deet-deet-deets.
你们对黑人群体的责任心哪去了
Well, where's your responsiveness to the community?
哪儿...
I mean, where's your...
行了  卡尔  开什么玩笑
Oh, come on, Carl. Seriously?
卡尔  等等  我们在这
Carl, wait, we are here,
为正义而战  我们就是这么做的
fighting the good fight. That's what we're doing.
各位不好意思  我需要打几通电话
Um, if you'll excuse me, I have some calls to make.
很高兴见到您  先生
It's so nice meeting you, sir.
那不是这家律所的出发点
That was not the point of this firm.
-现在我们...  -开什么玩笑  卡尔
- Now, what are we... - Are you serious, Carl? Come on, come on...
-黛安·洛哈特  -耶利米牧师  你好吗
- Diane Lockhart. - Pastor Jeremiah, how are you?
看见你真高兴
It's so good to see you.
你看上去真不错
You are looking well.
谢谢  你也是
Oh, thank you. As are you.
你看着真年轻
You get younger looking.
不不  是这个时代
No, no, it's the times.
这个时代让你斗志昂扬
It lights a fire in your belly.
再加上动感单车  快进来
That and a stationary bike. Come on in.
卡尔
Hey, Carl,
我都不知道黛安在这工作
I didn't know Diane was working here.
她在少年法庭上令人叹服  清一色法律援助
She performed amazing miracles in juvenile court, all pro bono.
你过奖了
Oh, you're too kind.
我估计卡尔已经把我的问题都告诉你们了
I imagine Carl has told you about my issue.
我还没告诉他们呢
Well, I haven't told them yet.
我们其实在讨论别的事情
You know, we were discussing other business.
那我一会儿再过来
Then I'll come back.
别  不用
Oh, no, no, no, no.
我们这就去会议室  让我的
We're gonna go into the conference room and let my, uh,
我的合伙人们讨论他们自己的工作
my partners discuss their work.
黛安  你也一起来好吗
And, uh, Diane, will you join us, please?
当然
Uh, certainly.
他在这待两周就走了
Mm. He's here for two weeks and he's gone.
忍着吧
Patience.
我经营了一个过渡房  是我教会的一部分
It's a transitional house I run, as part of my outreach ministry.
保罗又开始复吸了
And Paul has started to use again.
我需要把这个年轻人驱逐出去
Uh, that's the young man i need to evict.
我让他离开  但是他不肯
Now, I asked him to leave, but he refused.
我严令禁止
And I have strict policies
在过渡房里滥用毒品
against abuse in the house.
是的  一般我们不派发驱逐令  雷夫
Yeah, we don't normally deliver eviction notices, Rev.
我能处理好  阿德里安  用不了太久
I can handle it, Adrian. It won't take long.
你带上迪佩西亚  再加一个律师
Well, take DiPersia and an associate with you,
以防需要的工时比较多
in case it needs more hours.
-会的  -见到你真高兴  牧师
- I shall. - It's good to see you, Pastor.
谢谢你  黛安
Oh, thank you, Diane.
谢谢
Oh, yeah. Thank you.
驱逐令  我们通常还做这个
An eviction? Do we normally do that?
就是帮个忙
It's a favor.
会遇到麻烦吗
Are we expecting trouble?
应该不会
I don't think so.
其实  他说他会做的
Well, actually, he said that he would.
玛娅
Maia?
爸
Dad.
你好  亨利
Hello, Henry.
黛安
Diane.
玛娅  你有空吗
Maia, do you have a second?
没有  我在工作
No. No, I don't. I'm working.
没关系
It's okay.
聊一会吧
Take a minute.
你来这做什么
What are you doing here?
你不接我的电话
Well, you don't answer my calls.
那你就应该不要再打电话了
You should take that as a sign to stop calling, then,
而不是跑到我律所来
not as a sign to drop by my work.
别这样  玛娅
Please, Maia.
玛...
Ma...
你没事吧
Are you all right?
没事
Yes.
很遗憾你要经历这些事情
I'm sorry you're going through this.
谢谢
Thank you.
橄榄山
传教所
从黑暗走向光明
毒品测试
Drug test.
-你带枪了吗  -没有
- Do you carry a gun? - No.
用得上吗
You ever need one?
一直都能
All the time.
保罗·约翰逊
Paul Johnson?
-什么事  -你被驱逐了
- Yes? - You're being evicted.
要是我的话  我就捡起来
I'd pick that up.
否则呢
Or?
否则我就很礼貌地让你捡起来
Or I'll ask you politely to pick it up.
这是杰瑞德意思吧
So, this is from Jerry, huh?
真是个混蛋
What an asshole.
连这种下流勾当都要找人来做
Can't even do his own dirty work.
我们是伊斯顿牧师的律师
We're Pastor Easton's attorney,
-我们需要通知你  -这就是你告诉别人
- and we need you to know... - So, this is how you tell someone
你不想再给他们吹箫的方式吗
you don't want to suck their cock anymore?
我们需要通知你  先生
We need you to know, sir,
你已经违反了这个协议的规定
that you have broken the rules of this establishment.
是吗  那个只要他想要我就得操他的规定吗
Really? The rules that I have to fuck him whenever he wants?
他想赶我走的唯一理由
The only reason he's trying to kick me out
就是因为我结束了这段关系
is because I ended it...
因为我不想给一个70岁的老头吹箫
because I don't want a 70-year-old dick in my mouth.
闭嘴
Shut up
好好听清楚
and listen.
明天中午之前你必须搬出这个房子
You have until noon tomorrow to vacate the premises.
需要帮你找其它的住处吗
Do you need any help finding other accommodations?
告诉杰瑞他完了  我本来不打算做任何事的
Tell Jerry he blew it. I wasn't gonna do anything.
但现在我改主意了
Now I am.
他当然会那么说了
Of course he'd say that.
他说他准备要对这件事采取行动
He says he's going to do something about it.
做什么  联系个律师吗
What? Contact a lawyer?
麻烦稍等  莎芮瑟
Later, Sharise, please.
我觉得你可能会想见见这个人
I think you may want to deal with this.
加百列·科瓦奇  保罗·约翰逊的代理律师
A Gabriel Kovac says he represents Paul Johnson.
你好  科瓦奇先生  你好吗
Hello, Mr. Kovac. How are you?
还不错
Okay.
你得多准备些巧克力  少一些薄荷糖
You need more chocolate and fewer mints.
好吧  我记住了
Okay. Note taken.
梅丽莎会参与到我们的谈话
Marissa is going to sit in on this
并进行记录  如果你不介意的话
and take notes, if you don't mind.
多来点巧克力  记下来了
More chocolate. Got it.
同样地
Likewise and similarly,
我也要用手机进行录音
I have an iPhone here that I'm gonna record,
如果我能找到录音键的话
if I can, uh, put record on.
-在哪呢  -这里
- Some... - Um, there.
-那个按键  -很好
- That button there. - Oh, great.
谢谢  好了
Thank you. Yeah.
那么
So, um...
我是来代表
I represent
保罗·约翰逊先生的
Mr. Paul Johnson.
你的当事人长期占他的便宜
He has been fucked over by your client.
那是个法律术语吗
Is that a legal term?
占便宜吗
"Fucked over"?
不是  但形容得很准确
No. But it's accurate.
耶利米牧师把他的阴茎
Pastor Jeremiah placed his penis
放到了我当事人身上的两个开口处
in two of my client's orifices.
这么说怎么样
How's that?
你们哈佛教育的精英还满意吗
Hmm? Does that satisfy your Harvard education?
我没去过哈佛上学
I didn't go to Harvard.
我也没有
I didn't either.
你需要明白  提出这个控告
Uh, you do understand that by making this accusation,
卡瓦奇先生  你们可能会引来反诉
Mr. Kovac, that you are inviting a countersuit?
事实上  像这种没有依据的控告
In fact, a baseless accusation of this kind
也会成为非常好的理由
would be grounds to report you to
去向律师登记和纪律委员会举报你
the Attorney Registration & Disciplinary Commission.
洛哈特女士  事情是这样的
Ms. Lockhart, here's the thing.
我不是一个好律师
I'm not a great lawyer.
我考了三次才通过律师资格考试
Took me three tries to pass the bar.
但是我非常明白这一点
But I do know this.
你是被派到这来吓唬我的
You were sent in here to intimidate me,
因为你是典型的白人律师
'cause you're the token white lawyer,
通常都会用那些专业名词  什么纪律处分啊
and use all kinds of words like, uh, "Disciplinary action,"
还有法律诉讼啊
uh, "Court suits,"
想用这些东西把我吓跑
um, things like that that are supposed to scare me off.
我觉得你没有明白这不是关于
I don't think you understand that this isn't about...
我没那么容易被吓跑
I don't scare easy.
而且我对加入高档俱乐部不感兴趣
And, uh, I'm not interested in getting into the right country club.
我现在所知道的就是保罗·约翰逊
All I know is Paul Johnson,
他17岁的时候  被你的当事人
when he was 17 years old, was raped by your client,
一位注册牧师强奸了
a certified pastor.
伊利诺伊州的民法规定
And the Illinois civil statute of limitations
强奸的诉讼时效是20年
for statutory rape is 20 years.
那个是我自己查来的
I looked that up.
我还知道
I also know
你们并不希望这件事上法庭
that you don't want this to go to trial.
耶利米牧师可是一位牧师啊
Pastor Jeremiah is a pastor.
这已经是对他的双重打击
I mean, that's, like, already two strikes against him.
而那些自由党人士会看着他并且认为
And the liberals, they're gonna look at him and think
他会强奸孩子
he rapes kids.
不如你让他在法庭上穿他的牧师服吧
Hey, why don't you have him wear his collar in court,
这样他就肯定完蛋了
and then he'd really be fucked.
你想怎么样  科瓦奇先生
What do you want, Mr. Kovac?
钱
Money.
很多很多钱
And a lot of it.
我们不会接受勒索的
We won't be blackmailed.
不  你们会的
Yes, you will.
我们这也不叫勒索
We won't call it that.
我们称这个为审前和解
We'll call it a pretrial settlement.
对我们来说
And for our purposes...
我刚刚说的勒索都是在开玩笑
I was just joking about the blackmail thing.
我们只是在对审前和解
We are merely having a discussion
进行讨论
about a pretrial settlement.
很高兴认识你们
Nice to meet you.
你上过相亲网站吗
Do you ever go on eHarmony?
没有
No.
太可惜了
Too bad.
你应该去试试
You should try it.
没错
Yep.
我们必须和牧师安排见一面了
We need to arrange a meeting with the pastor.
你有在画廊和陌生人做爱吗
You ever fuck a stranger in an art gallery?
我只在这里和陌生人做爱
Hmm. It's the only place I'd fuck a stranger.
我以为你说这里只会有八个人呢
I thought you said there'd be eight people here.
是啊  刚刚人是不多
Yeah, there were.
你来得有点晚
You're a little late.
好吧  洗手间在哪
Okay. Where's the bathroom?
这只是从我们家洗衣筐里随便找的衣服
Yeah. It's just something I found in my hamper.
我真想住在你的洗衣筐里
Oh, I want to live in your hamper.
快  没人在看我们  吻我
Quick, no one's looking. Kiss me.
科林
Colin?
妈
Mom?
没错  老妈在此  本人驾到
Yes, Mom. Here I am, in the flesh.
介绍一下你朋友吧
Well, who's your friend?
她真是性感上天啊
She's very sexy.
这是我的同事  卢卡
This is my colleague, Lucca.
-卢卡  -奎恩
- Lucca... - Quinn.
-奎恩  卢卡·奎恩  -卢卡·奎恩
- Quinn. Lucca Quinn. - Lucca Quinn.
弗朗西斯卡·拉法特里
Francesca Lovatelli.
你们两个已经滚床单了吗
Are you two sleeping with each other?
-又来了  -我不是喜欢窥探隐私
- Uh, here we go. - I'm not in the habit of prying.
只不过科林从来不告诉我
It's just that Colin never tells me anything
任何有关私生活方面的事
about his personal life.
我也奇怪为什么呢
I wonder why.
我记得你说过会在绿色的画下等我
I thought you said under the green painting.
没错  我之前在啊
Yes, I did,
但看看我找到谁了  我儿子
but look who I found: my son.
你好  克莱伦斯
Hi, Clarence.
你们俩认识
You two know each other?
卢卡  对吗
Lucca, right?
你们没有雇我
You didn't hire me.
抱歉
Sorry.
克莱伦斯  来认识一下我儿子  科林
Clarence, please, meet my son, Colin.
-科林  这是我的新律师  -你好吗
- Colin, this is my new attorney. - Hey, man. How you doing?
妈  你在干什么  在画廊和你的律师约会
Mom, what are you doing? Gallery hopping with your lawyer?
你们看到特朗普干了什么吗
Hey. Did you see what Trump is doing?
我的天啊  这个国家  怎么了
Oh, my God, this country. What happened?
我听说他们在考虑标识出所有的穆斯林
I heard they're thinking of tagging all Muslims.
我知道  用微芯片
I know, microchips.
-我在考虑  成为穆斯林  -不行
- I'm thinking of - becoming Muslim. - No.
你觉得怎么样  卢卡
What do you think about that, Lucca?
你是穆斯林吗  也许你是
Ooh, are you Muslim? Maybe you are.
她不是  妈
Not a Muslim, Mom.
你会来参加明晚的生日派对吗
Well, are you gonna come to the birthday party tomorrow night?
我  什么
I, uh... uh, what?
没错  明天晚上
Yeah, tomorrow night.
-糟了  -生日会  明晚
- Oh. - Birthday party, tomorrow night.
我猜某人忘记告诉我这件事了
Huh. I guess someone forgot to mention it to me.
科林快要32岁了
Colin's 32 years old.
就像耶稣  还有一年就要面临死亡了
Like Jesus, one year away from death.
但他看起来还是像个孩子  看看这皮肤
But he still looks like a baby. Look at that skin.
我想卢卡可能会有点忙  我不
Uh, I think Lucca's probably a little busy. I don't...
没有  没有  我想我可以取消其它的安排
No, no, no. No, I-I think I can break that date.
-真的吗  -谢谢你  卢卡
- Really? - Thank you, Lucca.
我儿子就是这样  不是吗
Isn't that just like my son?
总是试着推开身边的女人
Always trying to push women away.
没错  可不是吗
I know. Isn't that true?
我讨厌他这点
I hate it.
你看到特朗普是怎么说非裔美国人了吗
Did you see what Trump said about African-Americans?
这个律师有证据证明
This lawyer has evidence
你去年付钱给保罗·约翰逊了
of payments you made to Paul Johnson last year.
付了三次  总计9000美元
Three payments, totaling $9,000.
这是真的
That's true.
所以你确实付钱给他了
So you made these payments?
是给保罗的封口费吗
Was it money to silence Paul?
不是
No.
好吧  那是什么
Well, then, what was it?
经文里讲过一位旅人
There's scripture, tells of a traveler,
被抢劫  遍体鳞伤
beaten, robbed,
被扔在路边等死
left at the side of the road.
唯一愿意帮助他的人是撒玛利亚人信徒
The only man to offer help was a Samaritan,
属于敌对的宗教组织
a rival ethnic group.
这个撒玛利亚人信徒关心这位旅人
Now, this Samaritan, he cared for this man.
这便是我做的
That's what I provided.
关心一个需要帮助的人
Care for someone who needed help.
我不能让他把这样的举动说得如此污秽
And I will not let him turn that into something obscene.
你有与他发生过性关系吗
You didn't have a sexual relationship with him?
没有
No.
我唯一做的  只是帮助他振作起来
All I ever did was help him get on his feet.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
我不相信他  卡尔
I don't believe him, Carl.
因此我知道我们不适合接这案子
And that's how I know we are not the right firm for this case.
你只为相信的人辩护吗
Well, you only defend people that you believe?
如果这案子处理不好
When the other shoe drops,
会有更多保罗找上门来
and more Pauls come forward,
在那时我们会希望从未踏过这趟浑水
we're gonna wish we were nowhere near involved with this.
我们会接下这案子
We are gonna take this case.
这事不能站错边  我们负担不起
We cannot afford to be on the wrong side of this.
你好好想想
Now, think about this:
黑人牧师强奸一位17岁的孩子
black pastor rapes 17-year-old child?
卡尔
Carl.
我要援引公司章程第四条
I'm invoking Article 4.
什么  你说什么
What? Excuse me?
我要求所有正式合伙人投票
I'm demanding a full partnership vote
决定律所的领导人选
on the leadership of this firm.
我们要朝另一个方向走
We're going in another direction.
你就是那个新方向
And you're the new direction.
是这意思吗  你认真的吗
Is that it? Seriously?
没错  我要拿回我的律所
Yeah, I'm taking my firm back.
你在带着它俯冲
You've driven it to the ground,
而在当下这种情况
and in this day and age,
我们不能让它走下坡路
we can't afford to let it drift.
你老了  卡尔
You got old, Carl.
而且你现在的行为是在背叛我
And you're betraying me right now.
但你知道吗  我依然尊敬你
But you know what? I still honor you.
尊敬你在过去做过的一切
Everything you've done in the past.
真的
Truly.
但现在你得放手
Now you need to go.
你可以做那些激励人心的演讲
You make those inspirational speeches,
收获属于你的掌声和赞扬
and you take every bit of that applause,
因为那是你应得的
'cause you have earned it.
但在律所未来的走向上
But as far as the future's concerned?
你得放手让我们来做  卡尔
You got to let us take it from here, Carl.
这20年来都不断有人说我老
You know, I've been called old for about 20 years now.
每次有人那样说我的时候
Every time somebody says that to me...
我会笑
I smile.
因为他们其实低估了我
Because they are underestimating me.
但你知道吗
But you know what?
你忘记了我教过你的东西
You forgot the lessons I taught you.
你完全忘记了
You forgot those lessons.
你得小心了
Now you be careful.
你说的这个老人
This old man
会狠狠教训你一顿
may just kick your ass.
我想你应该懂得这种体会
Yeah, I guess you can understand what it feels like to, uh...
律所冠着你的名字  但你却没有职能
have a firm that bears your name that lost your mission.
-我有这样的经历  -没错
- Mm. I've had my experience with that, yes. - Yeah.
所以你可能会明白我要做的事
So maybe you can understand why I'm doing what I'm doing.
所有合伙人会进行一次投票
Now, there's gonna be a full vote of the partners.
我需要你的帮助才能夺回我的律所
And I need your help, so I can get my firm back.
我们曾为了重要的事而奋斗  芭芭拉
We once stood for something important, Barbara.
而我们现在唯一关注的只是能否赚钱
And the only thing we stand for now is making money,
就我而言  这则意味着我们毫无意义
and as far as I'm concerned, that means we stand for nothing.
投我一票  芭芭拉
Vote with me, Barbara.
请一定投我一票
Vote with me, please.
阿德里安也有付出
Adrian, he'll have his input,
但就我而言  他如果是大脑你就是心脏
but he's the head and you're the heart, as far as I'm concerned.
帮助我一起将心摆在最前位
Help me put the heart first.
你知道我们要投票
Now, you know, uh, we're having a vote.
管理合伙人的投票
Managing partner?
我听说了
Yes, I heard.
你帮我查看下形势
Why don't you check out the lay of the land for me,
看看谁给谁投票
see who's voting for who.
我  我不想牵扯进来
I... Look, I don't want to get in the middle of this.
希望你能理解
Uh, I hope you understand.
我知道  我知道
Oh, I know, I know, I know.
那你为何不
Why don't you, uh...
多多留意下动向呢
put your ear to the ground.
雷迪克先生让我调查下这个瘾君子
Mr. Reddick asked me to see what I could find out about this addict
为什么会找耶利米牧师的麻烦
coming after Pastor Jeremiah.
尽管去查
Go ahead and do it.
别花太多计费工时
But not too many billable hours.
明白了
Understood.
他有问过我调查可能的得票数
He did ask me about a likely head count
管理合伙人里谁投了谁
for the vote on managing partner.
这你查起来有困难吗
Is that something you have a problem doing?
没困难
Not at all.
我只是想知道你希望我的调查有多准确
I just wanted to see how accurate you wanted me to be
我才能汇报给他
in what I report back to him.
加百列·科瓦奇办公室  执业律师
请上楼
感谢上帝没让我沦落至此
There but for the grace of God.
洛哈特女士  很高兴见到你
Ms. Lockhart, nice to see you.
欢迎
Welcome.
你不是梅丽莎
And... you're not Marissa.
梅丽莎在哪儿
Where is, uh, where is Marissa?
梅丽莎是我的助理
Marissa's my assistant.
这是玛娅
This is Maia.
玛娅  你好
Maia. Hello.
红头发很好看
Pretty red hair.
我有只红头发的狗
I had a dog with red hair.
快请坐  请坐
Uh, please sit down, sit down.
我才玩完一轮糖果消消乐
I am just finishing up a round of Candy Crush.
而这实在...
And this is...
我得玩完这轮  如果没完成的话
I have to finish this, if I don't finish,
我就会有点...
I'm just gonna be a bit of a...
稍等  抱歉
Hold on a second. Sorry.
见鬼了
Goddamn it!
今天不是我的幸运日
Not my day today.
科瓦奇先生
Mr. Kovac,
我们调查了你提过的钱款
we've looked into the payments you told us about,
耶利米牧师寄给保罗那些钱
from Pastor Jeremiah to Paul,
结果很满意  钱款的解释很单纯
and we're satisfied that there is an innocent explanation.
我们不会给约翰逊先生任何和解费
We're not gonna offer Mr. Johnson any money.
这是我们的最后决定
That's final.
是嘛
Really?
你叫什么来着
And who are you again?
玛娅
Maia.
你们总派白人律师过来
You keep sending out white lawyers.
-为什么  -科瓦奇先生
- Why is that? - Yes, Mr. Kovac,
你街头混混式的小聪明很令人印象深刻
we're very impressed with your street smarts.
但到某个时候
But at some point,
你总得停下那套反常青藤的把戏
you have to stop riding the anti-Ivy League thing.
你要么有证据  要么没有
You either have the evidence or not.
好吧  你得解释下
Okay, you'll have to explain this.
这是中途之家内部走廊的监控
This is the security footage from inside the Halfway House.
看看时间标记
And take a look at that time stamp.
耶利米牧师夜里十一点整进了保罗的房间
Pastor Jeremiah goes into Paul's room at 11:00 at night.
出来的时候已经
And he comes back out at...
十一点半
11:30.
期间过了半小时
That's a half hour.
我可能不是那么有礼貌
Yeah, yeah, I may not be polite,
但有些人比你想象中要糟糕许多
but-but people are worse than you expect.
牧师强奸小男孩
Pastors rape little boys!
即使是陈腔滥调也依然会发生
Even clichés happen.
是毒品检测
It was a drug test.
一次只针对保罗的毒品检测吗
A drug test that only targeted Paul?
那晚你没去其他人的房间
You didn't go into anybody else's room that night.
有人报告说保罗  也只有保罗
Well, there was a report that Paul, and only Paul,
大晚上有人拜访  可能是毒贩子
had a late-night visitor, perhaps a drug dealer.
所以我去了他房间做了毒品检测
So I went into his room to give him a drug test.
这是标准流程吗
This was standard procedure?
没错
Yes.
我们在房里就有做检测的设备
We have kits on-site that we use.
我去他房间没别的原因
I wasn't in his room for any other reason.
-能再放一遍吗  -当然可以
- Can you play it again? - Sure.
是牧师要求装监控的
The reverend is the one who put this security video in.
他想确保没人无视规矩
He wanted to make sure no one flaunted the rules.
说他毫无缘由地进人房间  这太疯狂了
It's insane to think he'd go into somebody's room without a reason.
暂停  就这里
Stop. There.
倒回去点
Go back.
漏了段时间
There's a time jump.
缺了快一小时的监控
You're missing almost an hour of footage.
这不可能
No, th-that can't happen.
但你看  时间标记跳了一小时
But look, the time code, it jumps an hour.
耶利米是个好人
Jeremiah is a good man.
他照顾好我们
He takes care of us.
他甚至会每天早上带我们去远足
He even takes us for long walks every morning.
帮助我们清醒大脑  不重蹈覆辙
It helps us clear our heads, keeps us in shape.
你为什么要说这些
Why are you saying that?
我没说不是这样
I'm not saying any different.
很多人想看虔诚的人被冠以污名
A lot of people want religious people brought down.
他们不喜欢上帝
They don't like God,
也不喜欢信仰上帝的人
or they don't like people who believe in God.
我只是想弄清楚事情的真相
I just want to know the truth.
去死吧
Then die.
这样你就能知道真相了
That's how you know the truth.
死亡
Die.
上帝会告诉你真相
And God'll tell you.
所以这里少了一小时得录像
So there's an hour missing.
-这意味着什么  -不知道
- What does that mean? - I don't know.
要么是有人在包庇牧师
Now, either someone is covering for the reverend,
要么是保罗·约翰逊和他的律师
or Paul Johnson and his lawyer
不想让我们看见
don't want us to see
-跟他交易的毒贩进了房间  -没错
- that his dealer entered the room. - Yeah.
等等  暂停
Wait, wait, freeze.
这是个笔记本  按一下空格键就行了
It's a laptop; just press the space button.
你想我把画面放大一点吗
Do you want me to enhance?
怎么了
What?
我刚在想我真的很适合干你的工作
I was just thinking I'm pretty good at your job.
我觉得我要去考个侦探证
I think I'll go for a detective license.
恭喜你  到底怎么了
Congratulations. What?
你看见这个没  这是个运动手环
Do you see this? It's a Fitbit.
你登上我的网站就能看见我什么时候在睡觉
When you go on my website, you can find when I was asleep,
什么时候醒着
when I was awake,
什么时候在走路  走了多远
when I was walking, how far I went.
看
Look.
好吧
Okay.
我会资助你考侦探证的
I'll sponsor you for a detective's license.
-真的吗  -当然
- Really? - Sure.
告诉我时间
Tell me when.
我不能恢复已经删除了的监控录像
I wasn't able to recover the deleted security footage,
但是梅丽莎发现保罗带了一个健康追踪器
but Marissa noticed Paul was wearing a fitness tracker.
-你好  我是梅丽莎  -你好
- Hi, I'm Marissa. - Hi.
耶利米给中途之家的每个人送了一个
Jeremiah gifted everyone at the halfway house one,
想让他们重视健康的生活方式
putting an emphasis on healthy living.
这个可以监视心率  计步
They monitor your heart rate, count your steps,
诸如此类  我以前觉得这东西很傻
things like that. I used to think they were stupid,
但现在我也带了一个  看见没
but now I have one. See?
牧师建立了一个活动组
Yeah, the reverend set up an activity group
让房客们相互比赛
for the tenants to compete with each other.
也就是说...
Which means...
我们能搞到保罗的所有数据
we have access to all of Paul's data.
这就是保罗的动向
This is what Paul was doing?
也不是所有的  但涵盖了一部分
Oh, well, not everything, but some.
这看上去像是保罗在睡觉  直到...
And it looks like Paul was sleeping until...
每日心率
你看见这里他的心率大幅上升了吗
you see that spike there?
这就是在耶利米敲门  叫醒他的时候
That's when Jeremiah knocked on the door, waking him up.
这并不能排除有性行为发生
This still doesn't rule out sex.
比对两人的数据就可以排除了
Not until you compare the data side-by-side.
保罗的心率在缓慢地升高
Paul's heart rate is slowly increasing.
而耶利米的心率在减缓
And Jeremiah's is decreasing.
这不能是两个人在发生性行为
That's not two people having sex.
能允许我失陪一下吗
Would you excuse me one second?
要么是耶利米一边在服用某种药物
Now, either Jeremiah somehow drugged himself
一边仍能占保罗的便宜  要么是...
and still managed to take advantage of Paul, or...
要么是保罗在撒谎
Or Paul is lying.
艾米  怎么了
Amy, what's wrong?
不知道  也许没事  我联系不上你
I don't know. Maybe nothing. I couldn't get ahold of you.
我爸一直打给我  所以我屏蔽来电了
Dad's been trying to call me, so I've been screening.
是的  他打到家里了  三次
Yeah, he called home. Three times.
每次我挂断  他又打过来  所以我只能接了
Every time I silenced it, he called back, so I had to answer.
他告诉我他一直都视我为家人
He told me he's always considered me family
然后谢谢我对你一直很好
and then thanked me for being so good to you.
-他在啜泣  -什么
- He was sobbing. - What?
听起来很像他在说再见
It sounded like good-bye.
我觉得你应该打给他
I think you should call him.
好吧
Yeah.
我们现在不在家  请留言...
We're not home right now. Please leave a message af...
*Some bright morning*
*When this life is over*
*I'll fly away*
*To that home on*
*God's celestial shore*
*I'll fly away*
*I'll fly away...*
爸
Dad?
在吗
Hello?
爸
Dad?
我知道你在想什么  好吗
I know what you're thinking, okay?
我现在马上赶过来
I'm on my way to you right now.
我们谈谈
Just... let's talk.
爸  我爱你  好吗
Dad, I love you, okay?
我在路上了
I'm on my way.
我很快就到了
I'm gonna be there soon.
别  别挂电话
Just... just don't hang up.
*Fly away*
*Oh, glory, I'll...*
别挂...
Don't hang up, just...
听我说
stay with me right n...
*When I die*
*Hallelujah, by and by...*
打给我妈
Try my mom.
*I'll fly away*
*I'll fly away... Oh, glory*
*I'll fly away...*
她没接
She isn't answering.
打去贾克斯叔叔家
Try her at Uncle Jax's.
为什么
Why?
她可能在那里
She might be there.
*When I die*
*Hallelujah, by and by*
*I'll fly...*
我们真的不必这样
We really don't have to do this.
害怕我会了解到什么吗  莫雷洛先生
Oh, afraid of what I might learn about you, Mr. Morrello?
科林
Colin!
生日快乐  儿子
Happy birthday, son.
谢谢  爸  这是卢卡
Thank you, dad. This is Lucca.
我知道
I know.
你妈妈总是提到你
Your mom's been talking about you.
特朗普难道不是一场噩梦吗
Isn't Trump a nightmare?
天呐  他关于「中央公园五罪犯」的言论
Oh. I mean, oh, my God, what he said about the Central Park Five.
1989年一名在中央公园慢跑的女性被袭击导致昏迷12天后死亡
五位有色人种青年被错判入狱
特朗普在媒体上呼吁重新纳入死刑
这是朱莉
Uh, this is Julie,
-我的秘书  -你好
- my secretary. - Hi.
你总是能雇到最优秀的人  爸
Always hiring the best, Dad.
你这话什么意思
What's that supposed to mean?
没什么  妈妈在哪
Nothing. Where is Mom?
在供应酒的地方附近  不然呢
Near the drinks. Where do you think?
很高兴认识你  卢卡
Very nice to meet you, Lucca.
我也是  拉法特里先生
Uh, you, too, Mr. Lovatelli.
「根源」是一本非常棒的网络杂志
The Root is a great online magazine.
关注美国黑人新闻  政治与文化的网络杂志
我在谷歌快讯上订阅了
I have it on Google Alert.
请不要根据今晚的事来评判我
Please don't judge me by this evening.
你说的太迟了
Too late.
卢卡  你好
Lucca, hello.
-你也来了  -好吧
- There you are! - Okay.
你一定要帮我解决一场争论
You have to settle a debate for me.
来吧
Come on.
科林  你好  生日快乐
Oh, Colin, hi. Happy birthday.
谢谢  妈
Thank you, Mom.
和爸在一起的是谁
Hey, hey, who's that with dad?
他的新玩具
That's his newest toy.
如果她不会让他中风我就没意见
I don't complain if it saves him from having a stroke.
卢卡
Now, Lucca,
我用谷歌搜了你  你真是挺特别的
I Googled you, and you are something special.
-是吗  -是的  你很特别
- Am I? - Yes, you are.
我很喜欢你在的律所  真的
I love your firm. I really do.
我想你和我儿子谈谈
I want you to talk to my son.
他一直都站在政府那边
He always sided with authority.
我从没有站在...
I never sided with...
过来  我们来了  大伙们
Come here. Here we are, everybody.
终于到了辩论时间了
Finally, the debate.
像伯尼·桑德斯的非裔美国人  没错吧
Now, African-Americans liked Bernie Sanders, am I right?
伯尼·桑德斯
美国国会史上任期最长的无党派独立议员
特别是年轻人
Especially the young ones.
如果不是有南方的州
And they would have out-voted Hillary
他们的票都会比希拉里多
if it weren't for the Southern states.
你同意吗  卢卡
Do you agree, Lucca?
我没有什么见解
I don't really have an opinion.
但是问题不是这个  问题是艺术
But that is not the question. The question is the arts.
没有艺术的话  就没有其他
All else fails without the arts.
玛格达莱娜  拜托
Magdalena, please.
你知道杰斯吗
Do you know Jay Z?
[说唱歌手]
我能失陪一下吗
Would you excuse me for a second?
你需要什么吗  卢卡
Do you need something, Lucca?
不  我只是去拿杯酒
No, just a drink.
我帮你拿吧
Let me get it for you.
没事的  我自己来
It's fine. It's fine.
她真是太棒了
Oh, she's wonderful.
太好了  科林
Wonderful, Colin.
你不娶她  我娶
If you don't marry her, I will.
-妈  -怎么了
- Mom. - Hmm?
能给她一点空间吗
Give her a little room, will you?
当然
Of course.
爸
Dad?!
Dad!
亨利
Henry?
爸
Dad?
亨利
Henry?
爸
Dad?!
Dad!
玛娅
Maia?
致我的家人
我的天
Oh, my God.
爸
Dad?!
Dad!
这是什么
What is that?
"玛娅  待在这里  通知警察
"Maia, stay here, call the police.
让警察来处理
Let them handle this.
我不想让你看到这些"
I don't want you to see this."
我的天
Oh, Jesus Christ.
爸
Dad?
我的天
Oh, my God!
天哪  发生什么事了  你做了什么
Oh, my God, what happened? What did you do?
-不要  别打电话  -喂
- Don't. Please don't call. - Hello.
我在西曼戈里尼街9511号
I'm at 9511 West Mangolini Road.
我们需要一辆救护车
We need an ambulance.
-爸爸  不要这样  千万不要  -玛娅
Dad, don't ever do that, okay? Ever! - Maia,
如果他们认为我试图自杀
if they think I tried to commit suicide,
他们就会撤销我的保释
they'll revoke my bail.
-你想自杀  -嘘
- You tried to commit suicide? - Shh.
玛娅  听我说
Maia, I need you to think with me.
如果他们撤回了我的保释
If they revoke my bail,
他们就会把我关押起来
they'll put me behind bars
防止我自杀  一直关到审判日
on suicide watch until the trial.
所以我只是摔倒了
Okay, so I just fell.
-你摔倒了  -对的
- You fell? - Mm-hmm.
你当时只是在检查屋顶  结果你摔倒了
You were checking the roof, and you fell.
我摔倒了
I fell.
是的
Yes. Yeah.
救护车马上就到
They'll be here in a few minutes.
现在  玛娅
Now, Maia,
你还有点时间
you have a few minutes.
我需要你让这里看起来一切正常
I need you to make this look right.
告诉医护人员他摔倒了  好吗
Tell the paramedics he fell, okay?
-完美  -你觉得恐同的
- Perfect. - Do you think it's all right
说唱歌词可以用文化因素来开脱
that rap lyrics are homophobic,
这样没问题吗
because it's cultural?
我不知道  克莱伦斯
I don't know, Clarence.
好吧  对了  祝贺你
Mm. Oh, by the way, congratulations.
这对公司而言是有利的
It'll be good for the firm.
什么对公司有利
What'll be?
在他的仕途上支持他
Being on his arm as he runs for office.
就像白思豪一样
It's like de Blasio.
白思豪为现任纽约市长
这不仅对他而言有利  对你亦然
Doesn't just work for him, it works for you.
好吧  我不太明白你在说什么
Okay, I don't understand a word you're saying.
他们将推举科林为参议员
They're gonna run Colin for senator.
这就是他担任助理联邦检察官的原因
That's why he's working as an AUSA.
这是成为参议员的跳板
It's a stepping stone to office.
你也一样
So are you.
有一个性感黑妞做女朋友
The hot black girlfriend?
这可是吸票的梦想组合
It's a demographic dream.
问问白思豪就知道了
Ask de Blasio.
谢谢
Thanks.
卢卡  发生什么事了  你要去哪儿
Lucca, what's going on? Where you going?
工作的事  我得走了
Uh work. I got to go.
紧急事务
An emergency.
好吧  我送你去
All right, well, I'll take you.
不用了  我已经预约了出租车
No, it's fine. I called for a Lyft.
替我给你的父母道歉
Apologize to your parents for me.
律师就是这样的  对吧
Work of a lawyer, right?
科林  快来
Colin, come in here!
*生日快乐  亲爱的科林*
*Happy birthday, dear Colin...*
我  我当时在想
I-I was thinking...
分诊护士去诊所
Triage nurse to E.R.
-我的天  亨利  -我的天哪
- Oh, my God, Henry. - Oh, my gosh.
你做了什么
What were you doing?
我们有屋顶修理工
We have people to check the roof.
看看  天呐  看看你
Look... Oh, God. Look at you.
我没事  真的  真没事
I'm fine. It's nothing, really. It's-it's... It's nothing.
你的腿
It's your leg.
你的背  都受伤了
And your back. I-It's everything.
我的天  如果我失去了你
Oh, my God, if I lost you,
我不知道该怎么办
I don't know what I'd do.
还有你当时怎么在那儿
And what were you doing there?
我想  想见爸爸
I wanted... I wanted to see Dad.
感谢老天
Oh, thank God.
如果他  如果他在那儿躺一整晚
If he, if he had been lying there all night...
你让贾克斯带你来的吗
You had Jax bring you here?
我  我不想等出租车
I d... I didn't, I didn't want to wait for a cab.
我自己又太心烦意乱  开不了车
I was too upset to drive myself.
你不能再这样了  妈妈
You have to end it, Mom.
贾克斯送我来这里又怎么样
What difference does it make if Jax drove me here?
你听到我刚才说的话了吗
Did you hear what I just said?
你不能再这样了
You have to end it.
不能怎么样
End what?
别装了
Stop that.
你懂我的意思
You know what I mean.
不管你怎么想我和你叔叔
Whatever you think you know about your uncle and I...
我怎么想不重要
It doesn't matter what I think.
重要的是我爸怎么想
It's what my father thinks.
你怎么知道他的想法
How do you know what he thinks?
什么
What...
"我写下这封信  并非是以委屈的心情
"I don't write this out of feeling wronged,
尽管我的妻子与我弟弟睡了
that because my wife slept with my brother,
我不觉得他们亏欠了我
I'm owed something.
是我背叛了我的妻子
It's I who's cheated my wife...
出于一种
out of what it feels like
被人所爱而回报以爱的心情"
to be loved by someone you love in return."
这是什么
What is that?
"我也背弃了我女儿
"Just like I've cheated my daughter of
我没能让她抬起头来
being able to hold her head up
她还是要为那些过错付出代价
and not be held accountable for the mistakes...
为她父亲犯下罪行付出代价
The crimes... of her father.
这两人是这世上我最爱的人
I love these two people more than anyone in the world.
我只想让她们开心幸福
I just want them to be happy,
实现这一点的最佳办法就是我的离开
And the best chance of that happening is for me to clear out
对她们放手"
and let them."
他让我发誓不告诉你他想自杀的事
He made me swear I wouldn't tell you he tried to do it.
你什么也不能说
You can't say anything.
亨利怎么样了
How's Henry?
走开
Go away.
-我只是想要确认一下  -滚开
- I just want to check... - Go away.
还有六个小时就要投票了
Look, with the vote six hours away,
这就是我们的立场
here's where we stand.
伊夫林说她的预算拨款太"吝啬"了
Evelyn says her expense allowance is "Stingy."
-吝啬  -她想增加预算
- Stingy. - She'd like an increase.
马克觉得律所已经脱离争取民事权利的根基了
And Mark feels the firm has lost track of its civil rights roots.
我喜欢雷迪克先生的说话方式
I love how Mr. Reddick talks.
真的
Truly.
但是我们得有资本允许
But we do more good in the world,
才能在这世上能做更多的好事
we have the capital to do good.
特朗普的美国一定不是我的美国  你呢
Trump's America sure ain't my America. Is it yours?
不  我们必须继续斗争
No, we got to keep on fighting.
如今我们正在挣更多的钱
So now that we're making more money,
我们不需要在预算开支上吝啬
we don't have to be so stingy on the expense accounts.
就像在塞尔玛那时一样  明白吗
That's the way we felt like in, uh, Selma, you know?
我们发现
We figured it out
有一个更容易的方法
there's an easier way to live.
我们每个人的力量
Each one of us
比不上我们团结的力量
is not as strong as we are collectively.
对吗
Right?
我说的够清楚吗  这不是什么难理解的事
Is that fair enough? That's not rocket science.
我后面的那位绅士
Yeah, the gentleman behind me...
抱歉
Sorry.
个人健康报告
正如你所见  科瓦奇先生
As you can see, Mr. Kovac,
这些是两个健康跟踪器的显示结果
these are the readouts from the two fitness trackers...
我讨厌这些东西
I hate this thing.
并且呼吸并不一致
...and the breathing doesn't match.
你当事人的心率正在上升
Your client's heart rate is increasing,
而耶利米牧师的心率在下降
and Pastor Jeremiah's is decreasing.
这表示他们之间没有发生性关系
That is not indicative of sexual relations.
我的天  败给你了
Oh, my God, you got me.
如果我是你  我会放弃诉讼  先生
If I were you, I would drop this suit, sir,
不然你会面临一场灾难性的反诉
or you'll be facing a devastating countersuit.
你知道你唯一的缺陷吗  戴安
You know the only problem you have, Diane?
有话就说
I can't wait.
保罗能够认出牧师阴茎上
Paul can identify a distinguishing mark
一个明显的标志
on the good pastor's dick.
这就表示他们发生了性关系
Now that is indicative of sexual relations.
你还想要反诉并把这一点提上公开法庭吗
You still want to countersue and take this to open court?
想的话就说
You just let me know.
我不会脱裤子的
I will not disrobe.
要证明他错了  这是最容易的方法  雷夫
It's the easiest way to prove him wrong, Rev.
你阴茎上没有胎记吗
Now you don't have a birthmark on your penis?
没有
No, I don't.
-所以他在说谎  -当然
- So he's lying? - Yes.
困难的是  牧师先生
The difficulty is, Pastor,
如果你不肯脱下裤子证明
if you don't disrobe,
这就给人做贼心虚的感觉
this will make you look guilty.
我明白
I understand that.
我不会脱裤子的
I am not disrobing.
你可以带一个相机
You can take the camera
照张照片就好
and take a photo of yourself.
我这一辈子都在抗争
I spent my whole life fighting,
为我们祖先不曾拥有的尊严而抗争
fighting for the dignity that was denied our forebears.
他们曾遭受的是这样的待遇
They were treated like this.
而我不会
I will not be.
这就是他所指望的
That's what he's counting on,
这个无足轻重的小人物
this little, uh... pissant.
他在敲诈你  他指望着
He is blackmailing you, and he's counting on the fact
你太过骄傲而不去证明他在说谎
that you have too much pride to prove that he's a liar.
他很聪明  也很正确
Then he's smart, and accurate,
因为我不会
because I won't.
那么我认为你应该付钱给他
Then I think you should pay him.
他会毁了你的名声的  牧师
He's gonna ruin your reputation, Reverend.
所有你为之抗争的尊严
All that dignity that you fought for,
都会像这样消失
it will disappear just like that.
你相信他吗
Do you believe him?
问题不是我相信什么
It's not about what I believe,
而是我们能证明什么
it's about what we can prove.
我问的不是这个
That's not what I asked.
牧师
Reverend...
我在这个圈子呆了很久
I have been around too long to know better than
我深刻了解英雄不是完美的道理
to expect anything from my heroes other than feet of clay.
不管怎样我都不在乎
I don't care one way or the other.
我只想打败这个混蛋
I just want to beat this son of a bitch.
这个健康追踪器与能追踪你路线的
The fitness tracker links to an app
应用程序相连  就像这样
which tracks your routes, like this.
这是我  在办公室里跑来跑去
That's me, running around the office,
告诉助理们他们的老板
talking to all of the assistants about
-给谁投票  -然后呢
- who their bosses are voting for. - And?
我获取了保罗·约翰逊过去两个月的
I was able to pull up Paul Johnson's tracking data
路径数据
for the past two months.
保罗慢跑的路线很随意
When Paul goes jogging, it's fairly random.
任意两条路线都不一样
No two routes appear to be the same.
但大约两周前  路线形成了一个模式
But about two weeks ago, a pattern started to emerge.
每周两三次
Two or three times a week,
保罗中途会在科瓦奇的办公室停留
Paul's routes included a pit stop at Kovac's office.
这很正常  他是他的律师
Well, that makes sense; he's his lawyer.
不  在我们给他送驱逐令之前
No. Paul didn't claim to have a lawyer
保罗没有律师
until we served him the eviction notice.
很好
Good.
我们需要对科瓦奇深入调查
We need to look deeper into Kovac.
任何诉讼案件  犯罪记录
Any lawsuits, past crimes.
看看能发现什么
See what you can find.
-完美的时机  -是的
- Perfect timing. - Yeah.
斯坦维女士
Uh, Ms. Stanway?
什么事
Yes?
您好  我们是雷迪克&博斯曼律所的
Hi. We're from the law firm Reddick/Boseman.
我们想问您几个有关
We were wondering if we can ask you
加百列·科瓦奇的问题
a few questions about Gabe Kovac.
有记录显示您几年前因侵犯人身罪起诉他
Records show you sued him for an assault a few years back.
是的  我们和解了然后我撤诉了
Yeah, we settled and I dropped the charges.
能告诉我们发生了什么事吗
Can you tell us what happened?
抱歉  我签了保密协议
I'm sorry. I signed a nondisclosure agreement.
如果我们保证不对别人说呢
What if we promise not to tell?
也许能行呢
Hey, you never know.
抱歉  失陪了
Sorry. If you'll excuse me.
科瓦奇为什么让你签保密协议
Uh, Why would Kovac have you sign an NDA?
不是他让我签的  是他的律师
He didn't. His lawyer did.
而且不是和他签的
And it wasn't with him.
是和他的雇主  第一宪章之选
It was with his employer, First Charter Choice.
-第一宪章之选  -那是什么
- First Charter Choice. - What's that?
一个另类右翼组织
It's an alt-right cause.
我漏掉什么了吗
Okay, am I missing something?
没有  是我漏掉了什么
No, but I was.
-你在给谁打电话  -阿德里安
- Who you calling? - Adrian.
他们要进行谈判了  快点
They're going into negotiations. Come on.
知道了  杰
Got it, Jay.
谢谢
Thanks.
干得漂亮
Good work.
随时
Anytime.
进来吧  先生们
Oh. Uh, come on in, gentlemen.
我想你们是终于醒悟过来
So, I guess you finally came to your senses,
准备和解了
and are ready to settle.
你到底知不知道律师注册和纪律委员会
Are you at all familiar with
道德准则第1.7条  科瓦奇先生
Rule 1.7 of the ARDC code of Ethics, Mr. Kovac?
距离我参加律师资格考试有段时间了
It's been a while since I studied for the bar.
要不  要不你给我总结一下
Why don't, uh... why don't you sum it up for me.
律师和当事人之间的利益冲突
Conflicts of interest between attorneys and their clients
可能导致被取消律师资格
may result in disbarment.
我和保罗之间有利益冲突吗
Do I have a kind of conflict of interest with Paul?
我们得知你和塞尔柯克先生的
We're aware that you have done business with, uh,
右翼法律基金会有生意往来
Mr. Selkirk's right-wing legal foundation,
第一宪章之选
First Charter Choice.
我们还得知塞尔柯克为了给这位优秀的牧师
And we're also aware that Selkirk subsidized this "Lawsuit,"
找麻烦而资助了这次"诉讼"
to embarrass the good reverend.
你拿了右翼势力的钱  科瓦奇先生
You're taking money from the alt-right, Mr. Kovac,
而且你把视频中毒品贩子的部分删除了
and you edited the drug dealer from that video.
你知道吗
You know what?
我想我们
I think we're, uh...
我们可以结束了
we're about done here.
而且我们准备对你和你的当事人
And we are prepared to file a civil suit against you
的敲诈勒索提起民事诉讼
and your client... for extortion!
祝你今天愉快
Have a good day, now!
你为什么不接我电话
Why aren't you answering my calls?
我一直很忙
I've been busy.
我的家人很疯狂
My family is insane.
不然你觉得为什么我不早点把你介绍给他们
Why do you think I didn't introduce you to them earlier?
这与你的家人无关
This isn't about your family.
问题在于我们的关系  它走到头了
It's about this relationship. It's run its course.
我不这么认为
I disagree.
那是你的权利
That's your right.
我不知道你在寻找什么  但我不是她
I'm not sure what you're looking for, but I'm not her.
我不是附属品  不是战利品
I'm not an accessory, I'm not a... trophy.
我也确信我不是妻子
I'm sure as hell not a wife.
我从未那样对待你
And I never treated you that way.
如果有人这样做了  我不会让他留在我身边
And if anyone ever does, they have no place in my life.
你把这件事小题大做了
You're making this a bigger deal than it needs to be.
我不喜欢你的语气
I don't like your tone.
我没有什么语气
There is no tone.
我们相处得很愉快
We had fun.
我们都知道这种关系不会维持一辈子
Both knew it wasn't for life.
我们不会"维持一辈子"
We don't do "For life."
我得走了
I have to go.
伊玛尼要投给雷迪克
Imani's voting for Reddick,
但卡尔文·司德瑞  尤妮斯和托米·内维尔支持你
but you have Calvin Story, Eunice and Tommy Neville.
我算过了  你领先一票
By my count, you're up one.
很好  谢谢
Good. Thank you.
朱利叶斯  给你留了个座
Julius. Saved you a seat.
-混蛋朱利叶斯  -谢谢  卡尔
- Fucking Julius? - Thanks, Carl.
是的
Yeah.
卡尔
Carl.
朱利叶斯·凯恩要离开律所了
Julius Cain is leaving the firm.
他没有资格投票
He is ineligible to vote.
第12条第四小节规定
Article 12, Subsection D puts forth
合伙人直至任职最后一天都有权
that full voting rights will remain in force
享有其完整投票权
through the last day of the partner's pay period,
我确信是周四才离职
which I believe is Thursday.
那么我们要开始
Well, then shall we commence, uh,
投票了吗
casting the ballots?
阿德里安11票  卡尔12票
11 for Adrian and 12 for Carl.
我想做民意调查
I want the room polled.
为什么  你输了
For what reason? You lost.
我想投票开除阿德里安·博斯曼
I want to vote for the removal of Adrian Boseman.
等等
Wait.
我没有投票
I didn't vote.
但我现在想投票了
But I want to now.
-太晚了  -不晚
- Eh, it's too late. - No, it's not.
卡尔
Carl,
你说过这是律所的心脏和头脑之争
you said this was a battle between the firm's heart and its head.
但并不是
But it's not.
这是过去和未来之争
It's about the past or the future.
你曾经的辉煌让我们受教  但是
Your past glories have a lot to teach us, but this...
这关乎现在
this is now.
斗争存在于当下  而阿德里安知道如何抗争
The fights are now, and Adrian knows how to fight them.
我投票给阿德里安
I vote for Adrian.
现在的情况是这样
So here we are.
打成平手了
We're split.
是的
Yep.
各占一半
50/50.
这会很有意思
This should be fun.
这就是当今世界的问题  对吧
Hmm. That's the problem with the world today, huh?
你认为当下的斗争不一样了
You think the fights are different now.
但你错了
But you're wrong.
他们是一模一样的
They're exactly the same.
喝一杯吗
May I?
敬理想主义
To idealism.
也敬实用主义
And pragmatism.
*They don't even feel like*
*Like going home*
*Yoo-hoo, well, boy, we'll stop along our way.*